(Leonard:)Well,
Sheldon always has his pants on.
(Amy:)I don't think I could
pick his knees out of a lineup.
(Penny:)Well, it's not
just the pants.
(Penny:)Just, it's like since
we got married,
(Penny:)he doesn't really
try anymore.
Uh, Penny?
(Amy:)I don't know how to say this,
(Amy:)but this is
my first girls' night
(Amy:)and you're kind of
bumming everybody out.
(Howard:)All right, got Halley to sleep.
(Raj:)Yeah, I heard you
on the baby monitor.
(Raj:)Didn't think you could
turn the theme from Walking Dead
(Raj:)into a lullaby.
(Howard:)Yeah, got to get her
hooked on TV,
(Howard:)or someday,
she'll want me to play outside.
(Howard:)Boy, that floor is so squeaky.
(Howard:)I'm surprised I didn't wake
her up walking out of the room.
(Raj:)Have you tried anything
to fix it?
(Howard:)Well, I put the rug down.
(Howard:)It didn't help.
(Raj:)I know. Blue shag.
What were you thinking?
(Howard:)Did try nailing a couple
of the boards down.
(Raj:)Did that do anything?
(Howard:)Yeah, it left little
holes in the floor,
(Howard:)that's why I
bought the rug.